luxyhair.com 2019-02-20

# Privacy Policy – Luxy Hair

We highly value our customers and their privacy. Our privacy policy is to respect and protect the privacy of our customers. Your personal information is safe with us. All personal information collected on this site is kept strictly confidential and not sold, reused, rented, disclosed, or loaned. Your personal information is used exclusively for the purpose of fulfilling your order and making your buying experience a success. Luxy Hair Co. ("Luxy Hair", 'we', 'our', 'us') respects the privacy rights of its online visitors ('you', 'your', 'yours') and recognize the importance of protecting the information collected about them. We provide this statement (the "Privacy Policy") to help you to understand what we may do with any personal information that we obtain from you. This Privacy Policy guides how we collect, store and use the information that you provide us with.By providing your personal information to us, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and agree that we may collect, use and disclose your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and part of, the Terms and Conditions, which govern, in general, your use of the website maintained and operated by Luxy Hair Co. (the "Site"). We will use your information only for the purposes set out below. Although we are committed to maintaining your confidence and trust in all of our activities with you, this Privacy Policy does not govern our collection or use of data about you through channels other than the Site. Please exit the Site immediately if you do not accept this Privacy Policy or are accessing the Site in a country or other territory where use of the Site is not permitted. We may need to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We recommend that you regularly check this page to ensure that you have read the most recent version.

### LEGAL PURCHASE AGE

If you are under 18, we require that you inform a parent or guardian about Luxy Hair’s Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions as well as requiring their consent to the Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions before placing an order with Luxy Hair.Our Website is not intended for use by children under the age of 14, and we will not knowingly collect any information from any person below the age of 14.

> Basically, if you’re under 18 years old, ask your parents or guardian before ordering please.

### TYPE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED

The following information is provided by Luxy Hair Co. to enable our online visitors to be fully informed of our Privacy Policies. The Site collects certain information when you interact with the Site. For example, the Site may collect "Personal Information" which is data that can be used to identify an individual, as defined by applicable law. The Site may also collect data that does not identify you specifically. The following is a list of data that we may collect and process about you:

    * Information that you provide by filling out forms on the Site. This includes information you provide when you order from the Site; subscribe to any services offered on the Site including but not limited to interactive services (such as blogs, chat rooms, message boards, or other user forums); enter a competition or promotion sponsored by Luxy Hair; complete a survey; or report a problem with the Site;
    * Your correct date of birth, which we may require that you submit accurately to ensure that you do not access the Site if you are not of a legal age to purchase items offered for sale on the Site;
    * Any information you may provide when you contact us or send us a correspondence;
    * Details of any transactions you carry out through the Site including the placement of any orders by you; and
    * Details of your visits to the Site including, but not limited to, your computer's IP address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system, password information, page interaction information, traffic data, location data, weblogs, and other data about the resources that you access.

  * We may obtain information about your usage of our Website to help us develop and improve it further through online surveys and other requests.

If an order is placed with us, we need to hold personal information including your name, email address, phone numbers, home address, shipping and credit card billing address(es) so that we can process and fulfill your order. We do not view or save your credit card or debit card information.

Additionally we may also obtain information as a result of authentication or identity checks. Sometimes we may ask for your telephone number. This number may be given to our courier for delivery services. These details allow us to process your order and to let you know the status of your order.

> Basically, we obtain some personal information from you for the purpose of your orders.

### USE OF COOKIES ON OUR WEBSITE

In common with many websites, we use "cookies" to help us gather and store information about visitors to our Site. A cookie is a small data file that our server sends to your browser when you visit the Site. The use of cookies helps us to assist your use of certain aspects of the Site. You can delete cookies at any time or you can set your browser to reject or disable cookies. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to the Site.

We use Cookies to keep track of your current shopping session, to enable you to proceed to checkout at any time and to personalize your online experience. If you do not accept Cookies you will be unable to use this website. Refer to the Help content of your browser for more information on selecting or deselecting Cookies.

> Basically, we use “cookies” to make your online experience as best as possible. Milk not included.

### HOW PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE USED

Luxy Hair may use your personal information for the processing of orders, payments and to provide you with a personalized shopping experience. We will also use your details to fulfill and deliver your orders. Personal Information that you provide may be disclosed to a credit reference or fraud prevention agency, which may keep a record of that information. Where there is a legal obligation to do so, we may disclose your information to any relevant regulatory body.

When you order from Luxy Hair, you will be offered the opportunity to opt out of our email newsletter and other update services. If you choose to opt-out for this service, we will not send you alerts for new products, features nor enhancements; special offers; upgrade opportunities; contests or events of interest. However, if you choose to receive our emails from time-to-time we will use the information you provide to promote the products and services via email. We do collate information about site traffic, sales, wish list, and other commercial information but do not share this information with any third parties. Finally, we may use your personal information for our internal marketing and demographic studies, together with non-personal data to monitor customer patterns so we can consistently improve our site design to better meet our visitors' needs. 

In addition to disclosures identified in the purposes above, from time to time we may disclose Personal Information to:

  * Our service providers and subcontractors, including our affiliates, retained to perform functions on our behalf or to provide services to us, such as warehousing and delivery; marketing and advertising; data processing; software development; website hosting and management; information technology and office services; legal, accounting, audit and other professional service providers; and further provided such service provider does not collect, use or disclose the personal information for any purpose other than to perform such functions or to provide services to us or as otherwise required by law;
  * Unaffiliated service providers with whom Luxy Hair may subcontract, including website hosting companies, fulfilment companies and other third party service providers;
  * The prospective seller or buyer of Luxy Hair’s business or assets, including where Luxy Hair or substantially all of Luxy Hair’s assets is acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets;
  * If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to: comply with any legal or regulatory obligation; respond to inquiries or requests from public authority; enforce or apply the Luxy Hair Terms of Use and other agreements; permit us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain; or protect the rights, property, safety or security of Luxy Hair, our employees, agents, contractors, customers, the visitors of the Site or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

> Basically, we use your personal information only for what is necessary and never share with those who shouldn’t see it.

### SECURITY 

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed. If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.

### CONSENT 

**How do you get my consent?**

When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only. If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.

You are solely responsible for any User Content that you submit. You are legally liable for the User Content that you submit including, for example, material protected by copyright, trademark, patent or trade secret law or other proprietary rights laws without permission of the author or owner or subject featured in such submission, or defamatory comments.

You grant to Luxy Hair the worldwide, perpetual, irrevocable, royalty-free, fully-paid, non-exclusive, transferable right to use your uploaded User Content in any manner to be determined in the Licensed Parties’ sole discretion, including but not limited to on its webpages, social media pages operated by the Licensed Parties, promotional e-mails and advertisements, and in other marketing, promotional and advertising initiatives, in any media now or hereafter known.

You hereby represent and warrant that (i) you own all rights in and to your User Content, (ii) if the User Content is subject to third party proprietary rights, you have all necessary licenses, rights, consents, and permissions to publish the User Content you submit and to grant the rights granted herein, including permission from all person(s) appearing in your User Content; (iii) you are not a minor, (iv) you are legally entitled to post the User Content, and the Licensed Parties’ use of your User Content as described herein will not violate the rights, including but not limited to copyright, trademark, privacy, publicity or other proprietary rights, of any third party or any law, and (v) the User Content is not libelous, defamatory, obscene, pornographic, abusive, indecent, threatening, harassing, hateful, or offensive. You hereby release, discharge and agree to hold the Licensed Parties, and any person acting on their behalf, harmless from any liability related in any way to the Licensed Parties’ use of your User Content.

The User Content that you submit is deemed non-confidential and the Licensed Parties have no obligation to maintain the confidentiality of any information, in whatever form, contained in any submission, except pursuant to the Licensed Parties’ respective privacy policies. By using the Services, you are consenting to Luxy Hair’s collection of any personal information you provide for the Luxy Hair’s use and disclosure in connection with the use of your User Content as described herein. If you do not agree to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in this way, please do not use the Services or otherwise provide Luxy Hair with personal information by contacting info@luxyhair.com. Your personal information may be transferred to servers located outside the country in which you live or to affiliates or other trusted third parties based in other countries so that they may process personal information on Luxy Hair’s behalf. By using the Services or otherwise providing Luxy Hair with personal information, you agree to such collection, use, disclosure, transfer and processing of your information in accordance with the terms of these Terms, the Privacy Policy and applicable data protection laws and regulations.

Luxy Hair reserves the right to remove any User Content from the Site, the Brand properties and the Services at any time, for any reason. If you believe User Content residing on the Site or the Services infringes a copyright, please refer to our Copyright Policy below. 

**How do I withdraw my consent?**

If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at info@luxyhair.com

### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website.

If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.

### WHERE AND HOW TO ASK QUESTIONS OR FILE COMPLAINTS

By visiting this Site, you are consenting and accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. If you require further information about our Privacy Policy, please go to the help section of the web site where Support Questions are answered, if you require more information please go to the Contact Us section of the web site and send an email to [info@luxyhair.com](mailto:info@luxyhair.com).

> Basically, by using our site, you agree to the terms on this page. Reach our team at [info@luxyhair.com](mailto:info@luxyhair.com) with any questions!
